This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After losing his brother Ace, Luffy fell into despair.
Weak! King of the Pirates!
Dammit!
I'm too weak!
However, after speaking with Luffy,
Rayleigh convinced him to return to Marineford
and deliver a message to his crew.
When the rest of the Straw Hats learned of his puzzling behavior
through an article in the newspaper,
they each found a new purpose in their journey.
Because Luffy wants to become the King of the Pirates!
And to help him,
I need to be the best navigator the world has ever seen!
Listen up, Luffy.
The Thousand Sunny isn't giving up.
Not ever.
And as our captain,
I know you aren't giving up either.
So let's sail.
Luffy,
when we meet again,
I'll be the best damn chef in all of the New World.
I'll make food fit for the King of the Pirates.
I will get much, much stronger!
Zoros pledged to his captain!
Antenagana Kingdom,
on Sword Mountain Island.
Ladies and gents,
feast your eyes!
What is everyone looking at?
Must really be something.
I heard they found some kind of crazy monster.
Come one, come all!
This is a spectacle you'll have to see to believe!
No organs!
No skin!
No eyeballs either!
Step right up and meet the walking, talking skeleton!
The strangest thing is,
it's only got one set of elbows!
Who knew such an anomaly could exist in this world?
Hey!
Do you think we're a bunch of suckers?
Give me a break!
Huh?
Did we offend you?
It's no walking or talking!
I'm not paying for this!
Yeah, it's just a stupid statue!
It seems Luffy's made up his mind.
There's no more time to waste,
for me or anyone.
Hey, Bonehead!
What's the big idea?
I'd better do something,
and quickly.
That's right!
Sing, tap dance,
anything's fine!
We can't disappoint this whole damn crowd!
But how can I possibly be of any use?
He already told you that, lazy bones!
Just get up and move around!
This is a rip-off!
When he saw me for the first time,
he wasn't afraid of my appearance in the slightest.
He reached out to me without hesitation.
Here's a question.
You ready?
Will you join our crew?
Yes, certainly.
I was overjoyed.
For 50 years,
I'd been drifting aimlessly
on those dark, lonely waters.
My shadow was stolen.
I don't want to hear you make excuses like that!
If you need your shadow back so bad,
then we'll get it back for you!
I'm so glad to still be alive!
Well, of course, right?
Ah, so does the offer to join your crew still stand?
Yeah, welcome aboard!
What?
Just like that?
That's real!
You'll never know how much that meant to me.
In that moment,
I realized that my 50 years of waiting
had finally paid off.
Where's our money?
Yeah, give it back!
Crap.
Those stupid skeletons hanging us out to dry.
Find them.
We'll just have to force them to get out.
Huh?
40 degrees!
That didn't go as planned!
They were right!
That thing is alive and it talks!
This is creepy!
What if it tries to eat me?!
Seems I can't go lower than 45 degrees.
I thought as much.
But if I can overcome that,
perhaps I can be of more help to Luffy.
Hmm.
Well, maybe there's an easier way.
He's playing a guitar?
Hey, that's cool.
Where did you even get that thing from?
You were enough of a damn freak show to begin with.
Let's tone it down a little, okay?
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
but spiteful words like those, they're harmless.
Why?
Because I have friends now.
Come on, everybody.
Life's a lot more fun when you're dancing to the music.
Hey, that's pretty catchy.
Yeah, he rocks.
I hope you all enjoy my rock and roll and new single,
you're bound to be a wild.
Meanwhile, near the giant bridge in the East Blue.
So you want to come to Baltigo with us after all?
What made you change your mind?
Well, whatever the reason, we're glad you did.
Dragon's been eager to meet you for a long time.
If I'd known the revolutionaries were so nice,
I might have come knocking on your door years ago.
We're sorry about that.
We gave it our best, but you were hard to track down.
What with changing crews and all.
I'm teasing.
Don't you worry.
In the end, everything worked out.
And I don't have any regrets.
Let's go!
Time to head out to Baltigo!
The sea's a vast place.
Some day, you'll find friends who won't ever leave you.
79 million berries?
Why does an eight-year-old child have such a high bounty?
They said she's one of the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who are plotting to end the world.
Really?
I heard she's saying six marine battleships, too.
She must have some kind of weird power.
Well, that explains the bounty.
We can't let a child of the devil run wild.
Okay, I'll be right over.
Why did you come to save me in the first place?
For the last time!
I don't want you here!
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
If that's Robin's enemy, then I know what to do.
Shoot down that flag.
No way!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the entire world and expect to win!
Yeah?
Bring it on!
Robin!
There's still something I want to hear you say!
Tell me!
You want to live!
If I'm allowed to say my wish just this once,
then I...
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
Please, Robin.
Come back inside.
You're going to catch cold out here.
I'll stay here.
Thank you.
After all, I'm a pirate and you're revolutionaries.
It's not wise to trust you yet.
I can't go into a cabin without any exits.
Robin!
There's no reason any of us would ever want to hurt you.
It's all right.
This is the way I did things back when I was alone.
Just let me stay.
Well, okay.
If that's what you want.
All right.
Go get as many blankets as you can find.
And get her some food and something hot to drink.
Make it snappy.
But we already set things up inside.
Hurry up!
And bring the sofa out here while you're at it.
Sir.
Luffy, do you think I can get stronger seeing the world through your father's eyes
by walking in his footsteps until we meet again?
This is the first time I've wanted to grow stronger for someone else.
It's not such a bad feeling.
Meanwhile, on the Bowen Islands on the Grand Line.
What's gotten into you, Usoppin'?
It's gotta turn all this fat into muscle.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Gotta get strong!
Because that's the only way to get off this island in?
Gotta get really strong!
Yes, you mentioned that.
Gotta get really, really strong!
Uh, how strong, exactly?
Really, really, really, really, really, really, really strong!
You're quite serious, aren't you?
But why the sudden change?
What did you see in that newspaper and...
Oh, Captain, sent us a message.
Messaging?
What are you talking about?
Get on already.
Huh?
Come on!
We're friends now, right?
LUPI!
Usopp...
I didn't know you were here, too.
Finish him!
Then we can all leave this place together!
I'll win no matter what!
You know, I never doubted him.
I just thought he could become king of the pirates with or without me.
Of course he could.
We're finally here!
We made it!
If we keep this up and sail around the rest of the world, we'll come to this wall one more
time.
And when we do, then I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
But I was wrong.
Not because he's weak, but because others are strong.
Even Luffy's not invincible, and he can't do everything on his own.
So, I have to get stronger to protect him and the rest of the crew!
Damn it, Heracles!
I need your help, okay?
Whatever it takes to improve myself, I'll do it!
Please, Master Heracles.
Huh?
M-Masterin?
That's right!
You have weapons, so teach me!
You're obviously a good fighter.
If you can survive on an island like this, tell me your secrets!
You...
You really think I'm a good fighter-in?
Sure!
I mean, you're amazing!
This is I!
Your Master-in!
Heraclesin!
I know that, but awesome!
Uh...
Please have a seat, Usoppin'.
Yes, Master.
Pay close attention, Pupilin'.
This forest is full of plants called Pop-Greenzin'.
They're known for turning hostile as soon as they sprout,
which you've no doubt noticed.
Now these are their Seedzin'.
What do you use them for?
Many things.
They each have unique applications.
Hang in there, Luffy.
Run, Usoppin'.
This forest is your training ground, and...
If it'll help you become king of the pirates,
I'll become the sniper king for real!
Meanwhile, on Gloom Island on the Grand Line,
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
Please!
Will you train me as a swordsman?
You disappoint me.
Stand up.
I can't believe you would ask your enemy for instruction.
Have you no shame?
Get out of here.
This is pathetic.
A pity, perhaps, but I overestimated your worth.
I said stand up.
You're making a fool of yourself.
Please!
Help me!
First of all, the baboons beat you.
And after that, you couldn't even make it out to sea.
I can't help you.
It's hopeless.
They didn't beat me.
What?
You're the only one left to take down.
But, I'm just not good enough to win against you the way I am now.
Anybody can see that.
I don't follow.
Clearly, you still consider me your enemy.
Yet, here you are, bowing down, begging for my help.
What do you mean to do?
Kill you.
Of course.
You admit you want to kill me.
And you expect me to assist you in that.
You're strange.
What a ridiculous request.
Aren't you the least bit embarrassed?
Perhaps your priorities are different now, Ro-Ro-Noah.
You, the ghost woman.
Go take care of his injuries.
Uh, what?
Why on earth would I take orders from you?
We'll begin after you recover.
Huh?
Mr. Fancy Pants treat me like some kind of maid?
What are you waiting for?
Let's go, stupid.
He's a fool.
But a man like that would not throw away his pride for his own sake.
He must be thinking of someone else.
3D is crossed out and 2Y is under it?
You're right, I see.
It's like a tattoo on his arm.
A while back, the whole crew promised we would meet up in a certain place in three days.
But we just couldn't.
So let me guess, 3D means three days, right?
Then, the 2Y is probably, um...
Two years!
I knew that!
So the meeting is going to be two years later.
All right.
It means he pulled that stunt in Marineford, knowing it would get him in the newspaper.
That way, he could make sure each of us got the message.
That was smart, especially for Luffy.
But none of us have what it takes to survive in the new world.
That's why we have to train.
So we'll all be stronger the next time we meet.
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to rest up?
No way!
See ya!
You saved me?
Who the hell are you anyway?
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm going to be King of the Pirates!
Until the day comes when I defeat him and take his title, I swear that I will never lose.
Is that okay?
King of the Pirates?
As long as I can still stand, I can train.
Let's get started.
There's one baboon you haven't beat yet.
They've mastered swordsmanship by observing humans.
They even organized by rank, all the way up to their master.
He's the leader of every baboon on this island.
That sword.
He learned to fight by copying what I do.
He's not like the others.
You should be cautious.
Sounds like fun.
You're nothing but a stepping stone, baboon.
The 我更在看里面。
The
See you at Sub-Alone in two years!
Plotting a course for his future, Luffy leaves Amazon Lily behind
and travels with Rayleigh to the deserted island of Ruskaina.
There, he struggles to unlock an arsenal of new abilities
as he goes head-to-head against the giant creatures that inhabit the island.
On the next One Piece, Luffy's training begins!
To the place we promised in two years!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!